<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">US Embassy Mobile</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- WelcomeActivity -->
    <string name="title_activity_welcome">US Embassy Mobile</string>
    <string name="welcome_title">Welcome</string>
    <string name="welcome_text">
        Welcome to the U.S. Department of State\'s \"US Embassy Mobile\"! This 
        is your source of all consular information for the U.S. Embassy 
        Warsaw, the U.S. Consulate Krakow and Consular Agency Poznan. It is 
        designed to help you quickly and easily find answers to your visa 
        questions, provide assistance to both resident and visiting U.S. 
        citizens, and supply you with the latest U.S news from the Embassy 
        news feed and twitter account. Get your answers right here, right now.
    </string>
    <string name="welcome_swipe_to_accept">Please swipe to the left to accept terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="regulations_info">
        To continue using the app please read the Terms &amp; Conditions below and press Accept
    </string>
    <string name="regulations_title">Privacy Statement</string>
    <string name="regulations_text_part_0">
    	We collect no personal information (PII) about you when you visit our 
    	site unless you choose to provide this information to us. Submitting 
    	personally identifiable information through our website is voluntary, 
    	but by doing so, you are giving your permission to use the information 
    	for the stated purpose. Not providing certain information may result 
    	in our inability to provide you with a service you desire. 
    	If you choose to provide us with PII on a Department website, through 
    	such methods as completing a web form or sending us an email, we will 
    	use that information to help us provide you the information or service 
    	you have requested or to respond to your message. The information we 
    	may receive from you varies based on what you do when visiting our 
    	site.\n\nWe do automatically collect and store the name of the domain 
    	from which you access the Internet (.com, .edu, etc.); the date and 
    	time you access our site; and the Internet address of the website 
    	(such as a search engine or referring page) from which you reached our 
    	site. We use the information we collect to count the number of 
    	visitors to the different pages on our site, and to help us make our 
    	site more useful to visitors like you.
   	</string>
   	<string name="regulations_text_part_1">If You Send Us Feedback</string>
   	<string name="regulations_text_part_2">
   	    You may choose to provide us with personal information via our 
   	    feedback capability. We use the information to improve our service to 
   	    you or to respond to your request. Sometimes we forward your e-mail to 
   	    other U.S. government agencies who may be better able to help you. 
    	Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, we do not share 
    	our e-mail with any other outside organizations.
    </string>
    <string name="regulations_text_part_3">Third-Party Websites and Applications</string>
    <string name="regulations_text_part_4">
        We link to social networking and other kinds of third-party websites. 
        We use social networking websites to interact with the foreign 
        audiences and to engage in public diplomacy worldwide. Social 
        networking websites are used to publicize embassy events, and engage 
        with members of the public. We also use web measurement and 
        customization technologies to measure the number of visitors to our 
        websites and their various sections and to help make our websites more 
        useful to visitors. In some cases, the third-party application may 
        request an email address, username, password, and geographic location 
        for account registration purposes. We do not use third-party websites 
        to solicit and collect PII from individuals. We do not collect or 
        store any PII collected by any third-party website, and no PII will be 
        disclosed, sold or transferred to any other entity outside the 
        Department of State, unless required for law enforcement purposes or 
        by statute.\n\nWe may use various types of online surveys to collect 
        opinions and feedback from a random sample of visitors. Primarily, the 
        State Department uses the ForeSee Results American Customer 
        Satisfaction Index (ACSI) online survey on an ongoing basis to obtain 
        feedback and data on visitor satisfaction with our websites. This 
        survey does not collect PII. Although the survey invitation pops up 
        for a random sample of visitors, it is optional, and not all embassy 
        websites carry the survey. If you decline the survey, you will still 
        have access to the identical information and resources at our site as 
        those who do take the survey. The survey reports are available only to 
        web managers and other designated staff who require this information 
        to perform their duties. We may use other limited-time surveys for 
        specific purposes, which are explained at the time they are posted.
    </string>
    <string name="regulations_text_part_5">Links to External Websites</string>
    <string name="regulations_text_part_6">
    	Our app may have links to other U.S. agencies, embassies, multilateral 
    	organizations, and private organizations in both the United States and 
    	other nations. When you follow a link and visit a website, you are no 
    	longer in our app and are subject to the privacy policy of the web 
    	site.\n\nEvery effort is made to provide accurate and complete 
    	information. However, we cannot guarantee that there will be no 
    	errors. With respect to documents and information on this app, neither 
    	the embassy nor its employees or contractors make any warranty, 
    	expressed or implied, including the warranties of merchantability and 
    	fitness for a particular purpose with respect to documents available 
    	from this app. Additionally, the embassy assumes no legal liability 
    	for the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of any information, 
    	product, or process disclosed herein and does not represent that use 
    	of such information, product, or process would not infringe on 
    	privately owned rights.\n\nFor app security purposes and to ensure 
    	that this service remains available to all users, this app may use 
    	software programs to monitor usage traffic to identify unauthorized 
    	attempts to upload or change information or otherwise cause damage. 
    	Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on 
    	this service are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the 
    	Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986. Information also may be used for 
    	authorized law enforcement investigations. Except for the above 
    	purposes, no other attempts are made to identify individual users or 
    	their usage habits. Unauthorized attempts to upload information and/or 
    	change information on these web sites are strictly prohibited and are 
    	subject to prosecution under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 
    	and Title 18 U.S.C. Sec.1001 and 1030.
    </string>
	<string name="accept">Accept</string>
	    
    <!-- Menu -->
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="language_en">EN</string>
    <string name="language_pl">PL</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>

    <!-- MainActivity -->
    <string name="title_activity_you_tube_player">YouTubePlayerActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_video_player">VideoPlayerActivity</string>
    <string name="main_activity_no_internet">There is no Internet connection. Content cannot be updated</string>
    <string name="main_activity_sync">Sync in progress. Please wait&#8230;</string>
    
    <!-- Toolbar -->
    <string name="feedback" >Feedback</string>
    <string name="toolbar_language_en">EN</string>
    <string name="toolbar_language_pl">PL</string>
    
    <!-- Videos Layout -->
    <string name="recent_videos">Recent video</string>
    <string name="most_viewed">Most viewed</string>
    <string name="videos_fragment_server_error_message">No videos available. Please try again later</string>
    <string name="videos_fragment_no_internet_for_video_play">There is no Internet connection. Video cannot be played</string>
    <string name="videos_fragment_no_internet_for_videos_download">There is no Internet connection. Videos are not available</string>
    
    <!-- FileManager -->
    <string name="delete">DELETE</string>
   	<string name="update">UPDATE</string>
   	<string name="send">Send \u00BB</string>
   	<string name="update_in_file_detail">Update:\u0020</string>
   	<string name="file_manager_server_error_message">Your files list could be out of date. Please try again later</string>
   	<string name="file_manager_no_internet_files_list">There is no Internet connection. Information about new files cannot be downloaded</string>
   	<string name="file_manager_no_internet_file_downloading">There is no Internet connection. File cannot be downloaded</string>
   	<string name="file_manager_file_error">File cannot be downloaded. Please try again later</string>
   	<string name="file_manager_file_detail_divider">" | "</string>
   	
   	<!-- Feedback -->
   	<string name="feedback_title">Feedback</string>
   	<string name="feedback_email">Your e-mail address (optional)</string>
   	<string name="feedback_content">Content</string>
   	<string name="feedback_send">Send \u00BB</string>
   	<string name="feedback_send_successful">Feedback sent to the server</string>
   	<string name="feedback_empty_content">Feedback content cannot be empty</string>
   	<string name="feedback_email_address_not_valid">E-mail address is not valid</string>
   	<string name="feedback_no_internet">There is no Internet connection. Feedback cannot be sent</string>
   	<string name="feedback_too_short_time">You can send one feedback per minute. Please try again later</string>
   	<string name="feedback_server_error_message">It is not possible to send your feedback. Please try again later</string>
   	<string name="feedback_description">
   	    Please share with us your comments and suggestions on your experience 
   	    using our Consular App through this page. If you have questions about 
   	    visa status or non-app related questions, please click here:
   	</string>
   	
   	<!-- Progress Dialog -->
   	<string name="progress_dialog_message">Downloading new content in progress.\nPlease wait&#8230;</string>
   	
   	<!-- Update Question Dialog -->
   	<string name="update_question_updated_available">Updates are available</string>
   	<string name="update_question_content">Updates are available for download. You can download them now and go to the main screen or update the content when the application will be started next time.</string>
   	<string name="update_question_update_now">Update now</string>
   	<string name="update_question_next_time">Update next time</string>
   	
   	<!-- Call Dialog -->
   	<string name="call_dialog_title">Do you want to call?</string>
   	<string name="call_dialog_message">You will begin to call phone number</string>
   	<string name="call_dialog_positive">Yes</string>
   	<string name="call_dialog_negative">No</string>
   	
   	<!-- Banner -->
   	<string name="banner_type_emergency">Emergency</string>
   	<string name="banner_type_security_advisory">Security Advisory</string>
   	<string name="banner_type_calendar_update">Calendar Update</string>
   	<string name="banner_type_new_media_release">New Media Release</string>
   	<string name="banner_type_general_update">General Update</string>
   	
   	<!-- Main screen -->
   	<string name="main_screen_welcome">Welcome</string>
   	<string name="main_screen_us_mission_poland">US Mission Poland</string>
   	<string name="main_screen_server_error_message">News and Tweets could be out of date</string>
   	<string name="main_screen_no_internet">There is no Internet connection. News and Tweets cannot be updated</string>
   	<string name="main_screen_no_internet_for_tweet">There is no Internet connection. Tweet cannot be opened</string>
   	
   	<!-- Article -->
   	<string name="article_layout_layout_name">Article</string>
   	
   	<!-- Server error dialog fragment -->
   	<string name="server_error_dialog_title">The service temporarily unavailable</string>
   	<string name="server_error_dialog_neutral_button_text">OK</string>
   	
   	<!-- News Fragment -->
   	<string name="news_fragment_server_error_message">News and Tweets could be out of date. Please try again later</string>
   	<string name="news_fragment_no_internet">There is no Internet connection. News and Tweets cannot be updated</string>
   	<string name="news_fragment_sync">Sync in progress. Please wait&#8230;</string>
   	
   	<!-- Passport Tracking -->
   	<string name="passport_tracking_passport_number">Passport number</string>
   	<string name="passport_tracking_send">Check passport status \u00BB</string>
   	<string name="passport_tracking_server_error_message">Passport status cannot be checked. Please try again later</string>
   	<string name="passport_tracking_no_internet">There is no Internet connection. Passport status cannot be checked</string>
   	<string name="passport_tracking_passport_number_empty">Passport number cannot be empty</string>
   	<string name="passport_tracking_description">
   	    After your visa interview at the Embassy, you may wish to track the 
   	    location of your passport. Please use the following form to check the 
   	    status of your passport.\n\nIf your passport is ready for pick-up, 
   	    please collect it in a timely manner and bring supporting 
   	    documents.\n\nPlease note that TNT Express will only hold passports 
   	    for 9 calendar days from the date that you receive confirmation that 
   	    your passport has arrived at the pickup location. Failure to pick up 
   	    your passport within this time may cause delays in the receipt of your 
   	    passport.
	</string>
   	    
   	<!-- File Manager Deleting Files Dialog Fragment -->
   	<string name="file_manager_deleting_files_dialog_fragment_title">These documents will be removed from the application</string>
   	<string name="file_manager_deleting_files_dialog_fragment_ok">OK</string>

</resources>
